What do you think about the trend of
guys adding HCG to TRT?
>> It's logical because the TRT clinic can
sell it at $800 a bottle. So, it's
another way for them. They've got slots
and if they try to fill every slot, they
can make three, five grand a month off
of each dumb patient. Like Brian
Thompson, the Liver King is a perfect
example of this. That guy had more money
than brains and they just ripped him the
[__] off. He had a b He had the dumbest
[__] cycle I've ever seen. It was so
goddamn dumb. He had redundant [__] He
had Anavar and Windstrol. He had GH and
secrets. They got him for everything.
That guy was dumb as [__] He bought it
hookline and sinker. It's just like all
that dumb [__] needed was testosterone
and GH. All the rest of it was
completely in the umbrella of what the
test and the GH did. You didn't need any
of that other [__] if you was testing
GH.
And then he overpaid for the GH too. He
paid like 10 grand a month for GH that
he could have gotten for 20 bucks for
200 bucks. Probably 200 bucks would have
gotten the same amount of GH as he was
getting for 12 grand. That's how much of
a ripoff HRT clinics are. So
the HCG
I got around it 10 years ago with um
sodium daspartate. So I've got a product
called Thor's hammer.
>> Absolutely. that I invented originally
it was called rise and swell for a
different brand and then I made it again
for my brand called the Thor's hammer
and that will
normally hcg will suppress LH release
whereas
um the sodium daspartate will cause LH
release and it will also stimulate the
um testes to produce testosterone
directly. So, I got around it in that I
found an over-the-counter product that
was as effective. It isn't as strong as
using a lot of hCG, but it's a
reasonable thing to use if all you're
trying to do is keep your testicles
alive while you're on cycle. And then it
does other stuff, too. So, you can keep
your balls the full size. And some
people see their their testicles
increase in size within 12 hours of
taking it. So, if all they're looking
for is a bigger balls or a bigger load
because their girlfriend likes a bigger
load, then that's an acceptable
alternative. If you want to use hCG to
protect your nuts, that's fine. But what
these guys don't know because their TRT
clinics are liars, is that that doesn't
protect your cerolei cells. It just
protects your latig cells. So, you're
not going to hang on to your sperm
count. This has nothing to do with sperm
production. This is just testosterone.
Nothing's going to protect your sperm
unless you're taking S FSH. And that
would be so mindn numbingly expensive
because there's no black market FSH that
it's basically you wait until it's time
to get someone pregnant and then you use
L you use the hCG and the FSH to get
someone pregnant. You can stay on a TRT
dose. And for people that have short
attention spans, I said the TRT dose
would be 20 milligrams of test, two
units of GH a day. you would just add to
the same syringe, you know, four or 500
micrograms of hCG and 75 FSH.
And if you can't afford to f 75 FSH
every day, do it every other day. I know
I say do everything every day, but with
FSH, there's a threshold effect. You
have to hit 75. Anything less than 75
doesn't trigger the threshold in the
test subjects. You could be an outlier,
but you don't know you're an outlier
until you've blown several months of a
fortune just to find out you're an
outlier. So rather than playing Russian
roulette with your pocketbook, just do
it the right way and use 75 minimum and
do that 75 as frequently as you can
afford. Don't short change it. That's
it. You'll get girls pregnant this way.
I've helped lots of girl guys get their
girlfriends pregnant or wives pregnant.
>> Yeah, absolutely. I I actually wrote a
book uh two years ago with that protocol
in there so that people could just have
access to it because there was just so
much nonsense about guys thinking they
needed to run hCG between when they
start TRT until when they want to get
someone pregnant. And it's like well not
only is that going to potentially cause
a bunch of side effects, but if that
worked then we wouldn't need fertility
protocols, would we? I mean if that
worked then it wouldn't be a problem.
Um, but it doesn't because the amount of
hCG you'd have to take to spill over
into FSH to get even any activation
dolly cells is like I I think it's like
1500 units multiple times a week to even
just get a tiny bit of activation. But
you're exactly right. If you ran FSH
indefinitely, you'd be broke. Um, so I
found that protocol, I mean, I publish
it on YouTube for free as well, put it
in my book so that everyone can copy and
paste it and take it to their provider.
I'm the only time I've seen it fail has
been when people had no chance of
recovering infertility like testicular
cancer, more obesity, stuff like that
where it was never going to happen. But
I' I've never seen it fail to date. But
when it comes to the hCG stuff, it it's
something that I' I've been glad to see
that it's kind of died out over time. It
seemed like it was a fad that kind of
came in and out and people seem to be
moving away from it, which which I think
is fantastic because it just creates
more problems and it doesn't really
solve anything.